what's wrong with me kids well it
qué pasa a mí chavalería bueno pues
seems like tortilla is
parece ser que tortilla la nos está
giving us more oil than we expected that's
dando más aceite del que esperábamos eso
good it's delicious I love you
es bueno está buenísimo te quiero
tortilla lan how I like
tortilla lan como me gusta la tortilla
potato tortilla I mean I love
de patatas o sea me encanta la tortilla
potato tortilla I love it turns out that there's
de patata me fascina resulta ser que ha
been a controversy that has exploded
pasado una polémica que ha explotado
a lot and I'm telling you this in this tone
muchísimo y os lo digo con este tono
because the truth is that it surprises me that
porque la verdad es que me sorprende que
these things I hope I have the internet
estas cosas espero tener internet a día
today but it's been a controversy that has
de hoy pero ha sido una polémica que ha
given a lot to talk about in the last
dado muchísimo que hablar en la última
hour it's gained a lot of attention
hora ha cogido muchísima repercusión la
people have exploded a lot auro in
gente ha estallado mucho auro en
bikini trend to all the
tendencia bikini a todos los canales de
salsa channels talking about this I've taken a
salsa hablando de esto yo he tardado un
little longer because I wanted to soak it you
poquito más porque he querido empaparme
know that the gameplay and
ya sabéis que el tema de gameplay y
things like that well it's not that I'm stuck there I
cosas así pues no es que esté pegado ahí
don't have to start seeing what's
no me tengo que poner a ver qué es lo
going on I've been all morning until
que pasa he estado toda la mañana hasta
a little while ago soaking it I've seen all
hace un rato empapando me he visto todos
the videos of sal yes I've seen all
los vídeos de sal se os he visto todos
the clicks and all the boys and all the
los clics y todos los chicos y todas las
things that there are to come to a
cosas que hay para llegar a una
conclusion first of all I want you to
conclusión en primer lugar quiero que
take some points into account and now  I
tengáis unos puntos en cuenta y ahora os
put into context what has happened in
pongo en contexto de lo que ha pasado de
the story and I will tell you more or less what
la historia y os diré más o menos lo que
I think but well let's see points
yo pienso pero bueno vamos a ver puntos
to keep in mind point number one the
a tener en cuenta punto número uno los
chats in this type of against I have not
chats en este tipo de contra no me dado
realized that the chats on some
cuenta que los chats en algunas
occasions are even more toxic than in
ocasiones son incluso más tóxicos que en
the content of sal ceo and I say this
el contenido de sal ceo y lo digo en
when it deals with issues of lordship as of
cuanto trató temas de la señoría como de
the youth infinitely they are more
la chavalería infinitamente son más
respectful and less shitty than on
respetuosos y menos mete [__] que en
some occasions in this series there are already
algunas ocasiones en esta serie ya van
several occasions such as the
varias ocasiones como por ejemplo en el
other day not like what we discussed in the
otro día no como lo que comentamos el
previous video Greg's chat when he
vídeo anterior el chat de greg cuando
went to attack a car and everything came back but there are already
fue atacar a auto y todo regrese pero ya
several occasions in which I
van varias ocasiones en las que me doy
realize how the chat puts my [ __ ] to such a
cuenta como el chat mete mi [__] a tal
level that it harms the story of
nivel que perjudica en la historia de
the creators themselves even
los propios creadores incluso llegando a
influencing their own feelings maybe
influir en su propio sentimiento a lo
a creator could react in
mejor un creador podría reaccionar de
a way regarding something that is
una forma respecto a algo que está
happening but the chat makes him give it a
pasando pero el chat hace que le dé una
twist and cause him to
vuelta de tuerca y que llegue a
react in a more radical way
reaccionar de alguna forma más radical
point number 2 I think that there are also
punto número 2 yo creo que también hay
many people who yell at each other very easily
mucha gente que se grita muy fácilmente
there are many people who I think have a
hay mucha gente que yo creo que tiene un
concept of aurum play
concepto de aurum play
one heart  and gameplay but especially of
one heart y gameplay pero sobre todo de
aurum and sarah not like they were
aurum y de sarah no como si fueran
care bears the 200 care bears
ositos cariñositos los 200 cariñositos
were little teddy bears that went around
eran unos ositos de peluche que iban
hugging everyone and there are
dando abrazos a todo el mundo y hay
a lot of people who met oro in the
mucha gente que ha conocido a oro en la
last season when he was dedicated to
última temporada cuando está dedicado al
gameplay and they think that now he is some kind
gameplay y cree que ahora es una especie
of care bears let's see he is not a
de ositos cariñositos a ver no es un
son of a [ __ ] he is not a toxic person he
hijo de [__] no es una persona tóxica no
is not a person who goes around insulting and
es una persona que vaya insultando y que
attacking others but he
vaya atacando a los demás pero tampoco
is not winnie the pooh either I mean in a way in fact
es winnie de pooh o sea en plan de hecho
humor if you have known her all your
humor si la habéis conocido de toda la
life rumors face a little bit and play some
vida rumores cara un poquito y gastarte
hooligan jokes and express yourself in a
bromas un poco gamberras y expresarse de
bit of a mischievous way I am
una forma un poco pícara es que estoy
surprised because there are a lot of people
sorprendido porque hay mucha gente
demanding a little tact in what has
reclamando un poco de tacto en esto que
happened and it is like he hasn't said anything I mean
ha pasado y es como no ha dicho nada o
yes he is expressing like in a
sea sí que está expresando como en plan
good vibes not trust buddy hey
buen rollo no confianza colegueo oye
clicking on us telling you I mess
pinchando nos diciéndote yo me meto
with you you mess with me I don't
contigo tú me metes conmigo no lo
really understand and aura comes to me
entiendo de verdad y a mí me viene aura
and messes with some of my  videos something from
y se mete con algo de mis vídeos algo de
my team something from my background something from a
mi equipo algo de mi fondo algo de algún
video that I've made well I'll give it back
vídeo que haya hecho pues yo le devuelvo
and I'll curse some of her videos you know like I'm
y me cago en algún vídeo suyo sabes en
not going to cry I'm not
plan no me pongo a llorar que no estoy
attacking the girl with the thing of not
atacando yo a la chica con lo de no me
going to cry because I know that there are people
pongo a llorar que ya sé que hay gente
who take the clicks they're going to post them
que cogen los clicks los van poniendo
however they want but honestly I
como les dé la gana pero sinceramente yo
think that girl that day was more
creo que esa chica ese día estaba más
sensitive than
sensible de la cuenta
necessary maybe charly talks about things in
a lo mejor el charly sobre las cosas de
other ways but it seems to me I don't know
otros modos pero me parece no sé
incredible and this comes up with
increíble y esto viene a colación con el
point number 3 that I'm going to comment on has
punto número 3 que os voy a comentar ha
caused this commotion on the
hecho que se forme esta movida en
internet about a church that they've
internet por una iglesia que han
built in my face let's see we're
construido en my cara a ver estamos
talking about a video game I've been
hablando de un videojuego yo vengo de
commenting on things in the last few weeks
comentar movidas en las últimas semanas
and months about a guy who
y en los últimos meses de un tío al cual
was fired from his job by calling him and
han despedido del trabajo llamándole y
labeling him an abuser
poniendo de la etiqueta de maltratador
breaking the presumption of innocence and
saltándose la presunción de inocencia y
to whom they have dedicated an
al que le han dedicado un documental
entire documentary trying to destroy his life
entero intentando destruir la vida hace
recently we were also commenting on the
poco también estuvimos comentando la
controversy of a kid who is dedicated to
polémica de un chaval que se dedica a
scamming his followers  promising them
estafar a sus seguidores prometiéndoles
things for the four night that he then didn't
cosas para el four night que luego no
fulfill or like for example one of the
cumplía o como por ejemplo uno de los
previous videos in which a
vídeos anteriores en las que un
youtuber has started to make fun of
youtubers se ha puesto a cachondearse de
the death of a child who has died of
la muerte de un niño que ha muerto por
brain cancer if after
cáncer cerebral si a mí después de
commenting on these things they come to me
comentar estas movidas me vienen
telling me that it has been tied up like this
diciendo que se ha liado así de tocho
because a girl has built a
porque una chica ha construido un
building in may cry the others have not
edificio en may cry a los demás no le ha
liked
gustado
doing that each one gives importance to
hacer que cada uno le da importancia a
what they want but listen to me it is a
lo que quiere pero escúchame que es un
video game or a game a contest to see
videojuego o un juego un concurso a ver
who creates the most beautiful town that I don't know I hear
cual crea el pueblo más bonito que no lo
that I already tell you that each one of you
se oye que ya os digo que cada uno
is in your right to give
estáis en vuestro derecho de darle a
each thing the importance that you want the
cada cosa la importancia que queráis lo
main thing here that I would take into account
principal aquí que yo tendría en cuenta
is that mía is a youtuber streamer who
es que mía es una youtuber streamer que
is in tortilla lan because sara has
está en tortilla lan porque sara ha
wanted to have her in tortilla she put her in
querido tenerla en tortilla la entro en
tortilla lan for sarah and also now she
tortilla lan por sarah y además ahora la
wanted her on her team because she knew that she was
quería en su equipo porque sabía que era
a crack in the minecraft subject the things
una crack en el tema minecraft las cosas
that a contest is held in each town
que se hace un concurso en cada pueblo
that you know that the tortilla
que sabes que los equipos de tortilla
land teams are being divided into towns
land se están dividiendo en pueblos no
the town does not have  The main thing is not where
tiene el pueblo principal no es donde
Aura
está aura
Guarnizo is and such, well, it is state-owned, nor the
guarnizo y tal pues está estatal ni a la
thing is that they organized a
cosa es que organizaron un concurso de
church competition, each town had to build
iglesia cada pueblo tenía que construir
a church and then someone would come, I think it
una iglesia y luego iba a venir uno creo
was a real priest, I think
que era un cura real creo que el dany
this Dany to check the church and see what he
este a revisar la iglesia qué tal le
thought and such, Auron in his team proposes
parecía y tal auron en su equipo propone
a church from a photo that they rescue from
una iglesia de una foto que rescatan de
Google, I don't know where, and Mia sends the
google yo que sé de dónde y mías manda a
entire town to collect the
todo el pueblo a recolectar los
materials, nor is it there at the moment when they
materiales ni a no está en el momento de
are collecting the materials but it does
están recolectando los materiales pero
appear at the moment when it starts to
sí que aparece en el momento de empieza
call, it begins by itself the
a llamar empieza por sí mismo la
construction of the church is the
construcción de la iglesia es la
creation of Adam from the Sistine Chapel.
creación de adán de la capilla sixtina
These chats had happened, I do what they have told
habían pasado estos chats yo hago lo que
me, not for love, up to
me han pasado más no por el amor hasta
here zero drama, okay, up to here there was
aquí cero drama vale hasta aquí no hubo
no kind of problem, the girl
ningún tipo de problema la chavala se
began to do her work by herself, she
puso a hacer su trabajo por sí misma
began to build the walls of the
empezó a construir los muros de la
church and all that stuff and the problem
iglesia y todo el rollo y el problema
begins when they go to check the
comienza cuando van a revisar las
structures and they don't like it, it doesn't give them the
estructuras y no les gusta no les da la
same impression as the photos, it would be a
misma impresión que las fotos sería
lot, let's
mucho
go outside for a moment, the outside part,
vamos a fuera un momento la parte de
Egypt, something like that, no, no, no, let's see Romanesque
egipto algo así no no no a ver románico
See, it's very Muslim, no, let's see,
a ver es como muy musulmán no a ver es
if we're going to make a
que si vamos a hacer una iglesia
Romanesque church, it's not worth it at
románica en plan no pinta absolutamente
all.
nada
Honestly, and this is my personal opinion, without
yo sinceramente y opinión personal sin
belittling the work, the hours, and what it
menospreciar el trabajo y las horas y lo
cost this girl to make
que le haya costado a esta chica hacer
this part of the church, these walls.
esta parte de la iglesia de estos muros
I honestly don't see that they are
yo sinceramente no veo que le estén
disrespecting her or
faltando al respeto ni que estén
treating them with contempt. They
tratando con desprecio a ellas
are simply saying that in the end,
simplemente están diciendo que al final
once it's built, it doesn't
una vez construido después no les está
give them the same impression as the photo.
dando la misma impresión que la foto que
Well, I don't understand it
pueden bueno tampoco que lo entienda yo
much either, because when it is, also from the
mucho porque cuando sí también de la
[ __ ] photo, if
[__] foto pues si te están construyendo
the same people from Campello are building it, what did they expect?
los mismos campello pues que esperaban
No, I don't understand it, but anyway, the thing is
no no lo entiendo pero bueno la cosa es
that once it's built when they come in,
que una vez construido cuando entran
you can or you don't like how it looks, but not like,
podéis o no nos gusta cómo queda pero no
let's tear it all down, let's
en plan vamos a tirarlo entero vamos a
send it all to hell, otherwise what they
mandarlo todo a la [__] si no lo que
're talking about is retouching and fixing
están hablando de retocar y de arreglar
some things, but I'm not
algunas cosas pero yo no estoy
hearing, for example, in these
escuchando que por ejemplo en estas
words there are things like, what the hell, we don't even
palabras haya cosas como vaya [__] ni
send you things, he doesn't know how to do them. They're
a te mandamos las cosas no sabe hacerlas
just saying, [ __ ],
no simplemente están diciendo [__]
well, I don't like it. Once here, the
pues no me gusta una vez aquí esto la
truth is that it gives me an impression that I don't
verdad que me da una impresión que no me
like the decision, nonsense. Let's remember that
llama la decisión bobadas recordamos que
everything  we are talking about this in the
todo esto estamos hablando dentro del
context that it is a game since a
contexto de que es un juego ya que un
[ __ ] game is that thanks to then
[__] juego sea que gracias a cabo luego
pay like croquettes there is even
a pagar como unas croquetas incluso hay
a moment in which biden mocks and
un momento en el que biden se burla y se
mocks louder of a gold cross that
burla más fuerte de una cruz de oro que
raul has made and that he has planted in
ha hecho raúl y que él ha plantado en
the middle of the altar of the church this gold cross that criticizes the only thing that I have done but nam nam no because gold is a symbol of power and raul offends us raul starts joking hey my cross on the
se pone a bromear oye mi cruz en la
dick my cross is wonderful and
[__] mi cruz es maravillosa y no pasa
nothing happens the thing is that if I stick I
nada la cosa es que si a mí yo me pego
don't know how many hours and these you know
no sé cuántas horas y estos sabéis que
what I'm going to say the truth because he moved
lo que voy a decir en verdad porque mudó
to mike it was with the fascist it has happened in
a mike era con el facha la ha pasado de
fact that they all piss me off if I
hecho que me cagan todos ellos si yo me
spend a few hours making
pongo unas cuantas de horas fabricando
something not with my effort with whatever I want,
algo no con mi esfuerzo con lo que me dé
dude you are already working you are
la gana caf ya estás trabajando estás
creating content but well if you
creando contenidos pero bueno si te
dedicate a few hours to creating something
dedicas unas horas a crear una cosa
towards something exactly as it is ordered
hacia una cosa tal cual está mandado
taking a photo and doing the same thing and they
tomando una foto y hacer lo mismo y
come and tell you that they do not like  what I would do is
vienen y te dicen que no les gusta yo lo
not start crying
que haría no sería ponerme a llorar yo
what I would do is on Aurum
lo que haría sería en el pecho de aurum
Play's chest and I take the wall that I
play y voy cojo el muro que he
built and put it on the [ __ ]
construido y se lo pongo en la [__]
door of his house you know I take the wall of
puerta de su casa sabe cojo el muro de
the church and I put it there on the
la iglesia y se lo pongo ahí en el
roof of his house in the village but I don't
tejado de su casa del pueblo pero no me
start crying I will answer him and I say
pongo a llorar ya le respondo y le digo
you are a son of a [ __ ] you are an [ __ ]
tú eres un hijo [__] tú eres un cabrón
well something at the same level like
pues alguna cosa al mismo nivel en plan
Elvis made from the game no but of course it
de elvis feito del juego no pero claro
turns out that the girl takes it in
resulta ser que la chica se lo toma de
a way that affects her a lot I
una forma que le afecta muchísimo yo la
respect her but I sincerely believe that she
respeto pero sinceramente creo que le
was on a very sensitive day or that the
cogió en un día muy sensible o que el
chat was conditioning her a little so
chat la estaba condicionando un poco a
that she thought that I was
que ella pensara que estaba
belittling her work insulting her or
menospreciando su trabajo insultándola o
something like that and it wasn't like that
algo por el estilo y no era así
really I don't like the facades I don't like it
realmente las fachadas no me gustan no
sincerely it's my opinion
me gusta sinceramente está de mi opinión
but if you like it so let's see if it's
pero si os mola así que a ver si es
true that well this style is very
verdad que bueno este estilo es muy
dirty it's not that it reminds me more
sucio no es que a mí me recuerda más a
of Arabs with
mí de árabes con
the dome on top and we put a little
la cúpula arriba y le ponemos un poquito
more it could look quite good
más puede quedar bastante bien
and basically so that it's not like
y básicamente para para que no sea como
everything so crashed like there is a space
todo tan chocado como que hay un espacio
to work out so to speak that we
para resultar por así decirlo que
can make a drop
le podremos hacer una bajada
and so we can invent it in the
y así nos lo podemos inventar en un
future it saddens me but we are not going to
futuro me entristece pero no vamos a
do anything guys they have voted they have
hacer nada chicos ellos han votado han
decided well this you have a lot of
decidido pues está tienes mucha
creativity for a town of
creatividad para un pueblo de gente de
simple-minded people you do not even know how to say
mentalidad simple no saben ni decir las
things you all say without empathy without
cosas todo lo dicen sin empatía sin
thinking what you can feel I do
pensar lo que puede sentir tú
not want those kind of comments
no quiero ese tipo de comentarios
[Music]
[Música]
you calm down neither we love to
tú tranquila ni a nosotros nos encanta
act and nothing because the girl
actuar y nada pues como la chica se lo
took it like that and it got so bad well people
tomó así y se puso tan mal pues la gente
empathized with her well they turned on
empatizó con ella bien se echaron encima
the other people from Aurum, Juan and
de la otra gente de aurum de juan y de
Sarah especially Sara as always
sarah sobre todo que sara como siempre
putting click giving them the
poniendo click dan dándoles el
meaning that I want to give it for
significado que yo quieren darle por
example this click in which she talks
ejemplo este clic en el que ella habla
to the same 8 saying no that if
con los mismos 8 diciendo yo no que si a
these people mess with me with something that I have
mí esta gente se meten con algo que yo
done well I do not start to cry I am
he hecho pues no me pongo a llorar estoy
in a game I [ __ ] on the top of his
en un juego me cago en lo alto de su
house I put a bomb on the door I
casa le pongo una bomba en la puerta le
put a carrot on the window what would you
pongo una zanahoria a la ventana yo que
call what I do but I do not start
se llamaría lo que hago pero no me pongo
to cry but  I accept the criticism I
a llorar pero yo acepto las críticas yo
start to cry and they took this
me pongo a llorar y han cogido este
click and they're rolling it on twitter
click y lo están rolando por twitter
as if to imply that he's
como dando a entender que se está
messing with nya with the girl then
metiendo con nya con la chica está luego
on the other hand there were also people being a pain in
por otra parte pues también había gente
the ass like the
tocando las pelotas como pueden ser las
four were from the daily forum a monkey that
four era del foro cotidiano un mono que
we will be this afternoon well I'm
estaremos esta tarde bueno estoy
uploading this video we are live and I will
subiendo este vídeo estamos en directo y
be reading the forum reacting a
estaré leyendo el foro reaccionando un
little the things they have put and of course she
poco las cosas han puesto y claro ella
explodes when they start making
explota cuando empiezan a hacer
donations to insult the one who is already
donaciones para insultar la que está ya
I would screw up spending the money on oil
me jodería gastarme la pasta para aceite
ar but it happens a lot in fact it happened to me
ar pero si pasa muchísimo de hecho a mí
too and she explodes ladies the
me pasó también y ella explota damas las
answers to these people putting
contestaciones a esta gente poniendo
other things both in the chat and in the
otras cosas tanto en el chat como en el
super chat and people with clip gestures
super chat y la gente con gestos clip
as if she were addressing them in this
como si se estuviera dirigiendo de esta
way and in this tone ania when you don't
forma y en este tono ania cuando no
look at the sudden and stop believing
fíjate los súbitos y deja de creer
media just because I'm his girlfriend not even
medios sólo por ser su novia ni siquiera
his fan where can she stand you are 30 years old let's
su fan donde aguanta tienes 30 años a
see if I can stand
ver si me aguante
what the [ __ ] this approach I just
what the fuck este enfoque acabo de
heard
escuchar
my god what a pain girl because I'm sure
a dios mío qué dolor chica porque seguro
you are  a girl
que eres una chica
looks
mira
hug
abrazo
[Music]
[Música]
those in the area forero [ __ ] you is
los de la zona forero que te jodan es
that I will [ __ ] you with envy or
que te [__] con la muerte de envidia o
whatever you have or your problems
de lo que tengas o de tus problemas de
really [ __ ] you with variable therapy
verdad que te jodan de terapia variable
this being is worth it don't be here you are asaja
a este ser se vale a no estés eres asaja
both one and the other have made it clear
tanto una como la otra han dejado claro
on their social networks that they have spoken
en sus redes sociales que han hablado
privately and that there is no fuss that is
por privado y que no hay quilombo que
worth it since there is nothing that there has been
valga ya que no hay nada que ha habido
a bit of a lack of communication when it comes to
un poco de falta de comunicación a la
creating what the church project is
hora de ir creando lo que es el proyecto
and such but how good that
de la iglesia y tal pero qué bueno que
nothing happens from my opinion okay
tampoco pasa nada desde mi opinión vale
but only from my opinion I can be
pero sólo desde mi opinión me puedo
wrong of course not even that has
equivocar por supuesto ni así que le ha
given a touch of drama and
dado un toque de dramatismo y de
victimhood to the matter I don't know if to
victimismo al asunto no sé si para
get the claim that people
conseguir el reclamo de que la gente
say oh we love you don't act like that which is
diga ay te queremos no te pongas así que
often liked no well for example I do
muchas veces gusta no pues por ejemplo
n't want to give more hype to this
esto no quiero darle más bombo a esto
because you already know everything but enjoy I
porque ya lo sabéis todo pero disfrutar
love each one of my companions and the
me encanta cada uno de mis compañeros y
town here is giving me I
del pueblo aquí está dando yo yo
consider that it is giving me one of lime and
considero que me está dando una de cal y
one of sand it is not like I am very
otra de arena no es como estoy muy
happy with my companion I love him
contenta con mi compañero lo quiero
very much  tata tata but don't give it
mucho a todo tata tata pero no le des
any more hype you know why cause
más bombo ya sabéis por qué causa que
they said they don't like the wall of your
han dicho que no les gusta el muro de tu
church that they haven't messed with
iglesia que tampoco se han metido con
your videos with your channel or with your face
tus vídeos con tu canal ni con tu cara
I sincerely don't mean any disrespect
yo sinceramente sin faltarle el respeto
to the girl and I understand that they didn't
a la chica y que entiendo que no
have a bad day or that at that moment it
tuvieron un mal día o que en ese momento
sat badly with them or the criticism didn't fit well
les sentará mal o no encajase bien la
but it
crítica pero es que me parece una
seems like complete [ __ ] to me I don't know maybe here on this channel it's that we have the same crowd and we're used to criticizing more hardcore it's worth coming from the controversies that I come from and seeing that movement because one has made a church in minecraft and
ha hecho una iglesia en minecraft y
because the others didn't like it makes
porque a los otros no le ha gustado se
me a little ballsy so nothing it's
me cae un poco los huevos así que nada
just that the subject ends here
es que simplemente el tema se acaba aquí
honestly there's not much more to
sinceramente no hay mucho más que
comment well yes there are things to
comentar bueno sí que hay cosas que
comment in fact we will be reading the
comentar de hecho estaremos leyendo el
daily forum the messages of some
foro cotidiano los mensajes de algunos
haters while they were uploading this
haters mientras estuvieron subiendo este
video it's live today okay on the
vídeo es hoy en directo vale en el canal
secondary channel but anyway here he
secundario pero bueno que aquí ha
showed a video a screenshot
mostrado vídeo una captura de pantalla
of such cool trips that they
de que viajes tan guays de que ellos
are perfectly fine and that here the
están perfectamente y de que aquí el
drama is  It's over, so it's like this,
drama se ha acabado así que ya está así
if there's no internal problem, there doesn't
si no hay ningún problema interno no
have to be an external one. Up to here is
tiene por qué haberlo externo hasta aquí
today's video, I hope you
el vídeo de hoy espero que os haya
liked it. It's also important to choose the
gustado igualmente es estar eligiendo la
comment box. Don't forget to
caja de comentarios no olvidéis
subscribe to all my channels to
suscribiros a todos mis canales para
find out about all the things that
enteraros de todas las movidas que
happen on the Internet. I'm sending it to sound.
ocurren en internet yo mando a sonar me